Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 1: Boxes 1-22
5583/3
Kheel Center
86.3 linear ft.
Records, publications.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Publications, manuals, policies, and plans issued by a large sample of Fortune 500 corporations and by a variety of organizations, such as professional and trade associations, government agencies, and educational and cultural organizations. The materials issued by corporations include company histories, employee newsletters, employee benefit plans, personnel practice manuals, performance appraisal forms, affirmative action policies, training brochures, job descriptions, and career development programs as well as national trade association documents and recruitment material.
Several economic activities(sectors) are represented in the collection, such as manufacturing, transportation, mining, banking, insurance, utilities, trade, and services. Corporations whose pamphlets are held in the collection include AT&T, Bethlehem Steel, Bell Telephone System, Firestone Tire & Rubber, Ford Motor Co., General Electric, General Foods, General Mills, General Motors, Goodyear Tire & Rubber, Heinz, International Harvester, Johnson & Johnson, Lockheed Aircraft Co., Maytag Co., Metropolitan Life Insurance Co., National Association of Manufacturers, Pennsylvania Railroad Co., Radio Corporation of America (RCA), Standard Oil, Tennessee Valley Authority, Union Carbide, and Westinghouse Electric among numerous other corporations.
Due to the volume of material in this collection the finding aid has been divided into four sections.
Section 1: Boxes 1-22
Section 2: Boxes 23-44
Section 3: Boxes 45-66
Section 4: Boxes 67-88
Boxes 82-87 have not been inventoried at this time.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Pullman Company.; Pullman-Standard Car Manufacturing Company.; Purdue University.; Quaker Oats Company.; Radio Corporation of America. RCA Victor Division.; Railway Express Agency.; Ralston Purina Company.; Republic Aviation Corporation.; Republic Steel Corporation.; Research Council for Economic Security.; Research Institute of America, inc.; Resistoflex Corporation.; Revere Copper and Brass Incorporated.; Reynolds Metals Company.; Reynolds Metals Company. Consumer Products Division.; R.J. Reynolds Tobacco Company.; Rheem Manufacturing Company.; Ritter-Conley Manufacturing.; Ritter Company.; Ritter-Pfaudler Corporation.; Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Railway Company.; Rockbestos Product Corporation.; Royal McBee Corporation.; Rubber Manufacturers Association (U.S.); Rutgers University. Institute of Management and Labor Relations.; Rutgers University.; St. Regis Paper Company.; Samsonite Corporation.; San Diego Gas and Electric Company.; San Francisco Employers Council.; Sangamo Electric Company.; Sargent and Company (New Haven, Conn.); Scott Paper Company.; Sealed Power Corporation.; Sears, Roebuck and Company.; Shell Oil Company.; Sinclair Oil Corporation.; SKF Industries, inc.; Society for Advancement of Management.; Society of Federal Labor Relations Professionals (U.S.); Socony Mobil Oil Company.; Socony-Vacuum Oil Company.; Solar Aircraft Company.; Southern California Edison Company.; Southern New England Telephone Company.; Southern Pacific Company.; Southern Regional Council.; Spencer Kellogg and Sons, Inc.; Sperry Gyroscope Company, inc.; Sperry Rand Corporation.; Standard Oil Company.; Standard Oil Company of California.; Standard Oil Company (Indiana); Standard Oil Company of New Jersey; Standard Oil Company (Ohio); Standard Oil Development Company.; State Farm Insurance Companies.; State Farm Mutual Automobile Insurance Company.; State Mutual Life Assurance Company (Worcester, Mass.); John B. Stetson Hat Company.; Stromberg-Carlson Telephone Manufacturing Co.; Studebaker Corporation.610:; Studebaker-Packard Corporation.; Sun Oil Company.; Supermarket Institute.; Swift & Company (Chicago, IL); Sylvania Electric Products, Inc.; Sylvania Electronics Systems.; Taylor Instrument Companies.; Tennessee Valley Authority.; Texaco, inc.; Texas Company.; Texas Instruments Incorporated.; Thatcher Glass Manufacturing Company.; Thompson Products, inc.; Thompson Ramo Wooldridge, inc.; Time, inc.; Time Share Corporation.; Timken Company.; Todd Shipyards Corporation.; Toledo Labor-Management-Citizens Committee.; Transportation Association of America.; Travelers Insurance Companies.; TRW Inc.; Tennessee Valley Authority.; Twentieth Century Fund.; Twin City Rapid Transit Company.; Union Bag-Camp Paper Corporation.; Union Carbide Corporation.; Union Electric Company of Missouri.; Union Labor Life Insurance Company.; Union Oil Company of California.; Union Pacific Railroad Company.; Uniroyal, inc.; United Aircraft Corporation.; United Airlines.; United Brands Company.; United Gas Corporation.; United Shoe Machinery Corporation.; U.S. Atomic Energy Commission.; United States. Bureau of Employment Security.; United States. Bureau of Federal Credit Unions.; United States. Bureau of Labor-Management Reports.; United States. Bureau of Labor Standards.; United States Civil Service Commission.; United States. Civil Aeronautics Administration; United States. Congress.; Job Corps (U.S.); U.S. Congress of Mayors.; United States. Department of Agriculture.; United States. Department of Commerce.; United States. Department of Defense.; United States. Department of Health, Education, and Welfare.; United States. Department of Labor.; United States. Department of State.; United States. Department of the Air Force.; United States. Department of the Army.; United States. Department of the Interior.; United States. Department of the Navy.; United States. Department of the Treasury.; United States. Federal Trade Commission.; United States.General Accounting Office.; United States. General Services Administration.; United States. Internal Revenue Service.; United States. Interstate Commerce Commission.; Library of Congress; United States. National Labor Board.; United States.Office of Economic Opportunity.; United States. Railroad Retirement Board.; United States Rubber Company.; United States. Securities and Exchange Commission.; United States. Small Business Administration.; United States. Social Security Administration.; United States. Social Security Board.; United States Steel Corporation.; United States.Veterans Administration.; Volunteers in Service to America.; University of San Francisco.; Upjohn Company.; W.E. Upjohn Institute for Employment Research.; Upjohn Institute for Community Research.; Workmen's Compensation Board of Vancouver (B.C.); Victor Adding Machine Co.; University of Washington.; Washington University (Saint Louis, Mo.); Wayne State University.; Weirton Steel Corporation.; Welch's; University of the West Indies; West Virginia Pulp and Paper Company.; Western Electric Company.; Western Michigan University; Western Railways.; Western Union Telegraph Company.; Westinghouse Electric & Manufacturing Company.; Weston Electrical Company.; Weyerhaeuser Timber Company.; George Wiedemann Brewing Company.; H.W. Wilson Company; Wisconsin Electric Power Company; University of Wisconsin.; Wyandotte Chemicals Corporation.; Xerox Corporation.; Yale Towne Manufacturing Company; Yale University; Youngstown Sheet and Tube Company.; Zenith Radio Corporation.
Subjects:
Adult education; Aeronautics; Agricultural industries; Aluminum industry and trade; Airlines; Aircraft industry; Agricultural machinery; Architectural metal-work; Automobile industry and trade; Arbitration, Industrial; Agricultural chemicals industry; Audio equipment industry; Bituminous materials industry; Building trades; Buildings -- Environmental engineering; Banks and banking; Breweries; Baked products industry; Business consultants; Clothing trade; Coal mines and mining; Chemical industry; Compressor industry; Clerks (Retail trade); Computer industry; Cereal products; Consumer protection; Container industry; Credit unions; Clay industries; Cement industries; Copper alloys; Dairy products industry; Detergent industry; Executives --Training of; Electric power transmission; Electronics industries; Food industry and trade; Frozen foods and industry; Footwear industry; Fruit trade; Farm produce --Marketing -- Government policy; Finance, Public; Glass container industry; Glass manufacture; Gas extraction; Grain trade; Grocery trade; Gasket industry; Human capital; Hydroelectric power plants; Life insurance.; Iron industry and trade; Property insurance.; Casualty insurance.; Instructional materials industry; Health insurance.; Investment banking; Infant formula industry; Knit good industry; Labor unions; Local transit; Luggage industry; Logging; Medical supplies industry; Medicaid; Motor vehicle industry; Metal trade; Meat industry and trade; Military vehicle industry; Medical instruments and apparatus industry; Management; Measuring instruments; Natural gas pipelines; Notions (Merchandise); Newspaper publishing; Navigation equipment industry; National security; Office management; Office equipment and supplies; Petroleum refineries; Photographic industry; Paper folding (Graphic design); Public utilities; Paper products industry; Political participation; Plastics industry and trade; Pharmaceutical industry; Paint industry and trade; Public administration; Public opinion polls; Paper bag industry; Retail trade; Rug and carpet industry; Railroads; Rubber industry and trade; Railroad equipment industry; Roller bearings; Security systems industry; Service industries; Shipment of goods; Sanitary supply industry; Soybean industry; Slaughtering and slaughter-houses; Telecommunication.; Transportation equipment industry.; Trucking industry.; Trucks -- Design and construction.; Textile industry.; Trade associations.; Tobacco industry.; Universities and colleges.; Vocational education.; Wood products.; Welding equipment industry.; Woolen goods industry.
Form and Genre Terms:
Records.; Publications
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
RELATED MATERIALS
Other sections of this Collection:
5583/3: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3 5583/3: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 2: Boxes 23-44
5583/3: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 3: Boxes 45-66
5583/3: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 4: Boxes 67-88
Boxes 82-87 have not been inventoried at this point.
Related Collections:
5583/1: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 1
5583/2: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 2
5583/4: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 4. Corporate and Organizational Publications
5583/5: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5
5583/6: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 6
5880: Archives Organization File (AOF) V, Additional Company Documents
5956: Archives Organization File Additional records
CONTAINER LIST
- Box: 1, Folder: 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Foreman Tells Management's Story, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Otis C. McCreery & Arthur M. Doty
    Format: Publication
    Language: English.
- Box: 1, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Materials Handling, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Box: 1, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Indoctrination and Training of Secretarial and Clerical Employees, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Box: 1, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: New Foreman: Selection, Training and Development, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Box: 1, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Office Supervisory Training Program, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Box: 1, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Operations Improvement, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Box: 1, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Costs and Cost Control Series VI, 1954; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Box: 1, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Manual for the Training of Job Trainers, 1956; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Box: 1, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Secretarial and Clerical Handbook, 1964; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Box: 1, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Conference Leader Training Manual, 1957; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Box: 1, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Safety Vol. II Leader's Guide, 1956; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Box: 1, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Conference Leader Training Manual for the Conference Director, 1956; Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Box: 1, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Employees' Retirement Plan for Salaried Employees of Aluminum Company of America and Subsidiary Companies, 1954; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Box: 1, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Employees' Retirement Plan for Hourly Rated Employees of Aluminum Company of America and Subsidiary Companies, 1954; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Box: 1, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: A Report on Our Business Year, 1950; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Box: 1, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: A Career for You with ALCOA, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Box: 1, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: ECI Error-Cause Identification and Removal, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Box: 1, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Employee Opinion Surveys, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Box: 1, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Zero Defects Story, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Box: 1, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Careers in Mechanical Engineering, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Box: 1, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Careers in Industrial Engineering, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Box: 1, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Career Facts, 1974; Publication (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Box: 1, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Alcoa is Opportunity, 1975; Publication (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Box: 1, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Careers in Customer Service, 1971; Publication (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Box: 1, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Careers in Management Information Services, 1971; Publication (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Box: 1, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Careers in Industrial Marketing, 1971; Publication (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Box: 1, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Careers in Traffic Management, 1971; Publication (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Box: 1, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Careers in Chemical Engineering, 1971; Publication (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Box: 1, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Careers in Production Control, 1971; Publication (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Box: 1, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Careers in Electrical and Electronics Engineering, 1971; Publication (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Box: 1, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Career Facts, 1971; Publication (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Box: 1, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Job Training Foreman Report, 1957; Publication (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Box: 1, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Manual For Meetings Series XXV- Office Supervisory Series, 1959; Publication (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Box: 1, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Alcoa Saving Pan for Eligible Salaried Employees, 1959; Publication (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Box: 1, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Supplemental Unemployment Benefits, 1957; Publication (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Box: 1, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Crane Operators' Training Program, 1957; Publication (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Box: 1, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Job Training Foreman Report, 1955; Publication (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Box: 1, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Job Training Foreman Report, 1953; Publication (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Box: 1, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Employees' Retirement Plan of Aluminum Company of America IA, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Box: 1, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Employees' Retirement Plan of Aluminum Company of America Plan IIA, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Box: 1, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Additional Vacation Benefits Plan for Salaried Employees, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Box: 1, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Alcoa Handbook for Salaried Employees on Foreign Assignments, 1974; Publication (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Box: 1, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Wage Chronology: Aluminimum Company of America 1968-70, 1971; Publication (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Box: 2, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Local Communications Exchange No.22, 1969; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Box: 2, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Back Case Accidents, 1965; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Box: 2, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Job Description and Classification Manual for Hourly Rated Production, Maintenance and Clerical Jobs, 1967; Publication (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Box: 2, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Job Description and Classification Manual for Salaried Jobs, 1967; Publication (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Box: 2, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Labor Relations, 1963; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Box: 2, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Financial Review 1965, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Box: 2, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Getting Performance that Pays Off, 1962; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Box: 2, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Container Manufacturing Division Management Trainee Program, 1967; Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Box: 2, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Supervisory Discussion Program: Conference Leaders Guide, 1967; Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Box: 2, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Seminar Training (Internal Correspondence), 1965; Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Box: 2, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Supplemental Group Life Insurance Plan, 1965; Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Box: 2, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Retirement Program for Salaried Employees, 1969; Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Box: 2, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Your Basic Group Life & Comprehensive Medical Expense Insurance Plan, 1969; Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Box: 2, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Canco Products Manufacturing Management Trainee Program, 1965; Publication (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Box: 2, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Training Workers to Get Results, 1967; Publication (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Box: 2, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: The Money a Canco Job is Worth, 1962; Publication (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Box: 2, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Comptroller's Department Management Trainee Program, 1967; Publication (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Box: 2, Folder: 18, Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Item 1: Glass Products Manufacturing Management Trainee Program, 1965; Publication (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Box: 2, Folder: 19, Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Item 1: Canco Products Manufacturing Cooperative Student Training Program, 1966; Publication (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Box: 2, Folder: 20, Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Item 1: Container Manufacturing Division Management Trainee Program Lithographic Trainee, 1963; Publication (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Box: 2, Folder: 21, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Item 1: Canco Newsletter No.26, Publication (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Box: 2, Folder: 22, Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Item 1: Canco Newsletter No.34, 1962; Publication (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Box: 2, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Canco Newsletter No.40, 1964; Publication (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Box: 2, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Pension Plan, 1955; Publication (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Box: 2, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: The Management Point of View of an Apprenticeship Program, Publication (Box 2, Folder 25)
    Author: E.S. Coleman
- Box: 2, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Facts About Your Company's Benefit Plan, Publication (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Box: 2, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Plan for Employees' Pensions, Disability Benefits and Death Benefits, 1961; Publication (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Box: 2, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: Payroll Deductions for Employees' Savings, 1951; Publication (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Box: 2, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Group Life Insurance with Double Indemnity For Accidental Death, 1963; Publication (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Box: 2, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Plan for Employees' Pensions, Disability Benefits and Death Benefits, 1952; Publication (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Box: 2, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: A Description of the Armco Operation at Middletown Works, 1958; Publication (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Box: 2, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: As I See Armco Policies, 1955; Publication (Box 2, Folder 32)
    Author: W.F. Johnston
- Box: 2, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: The Armco Wage Payment Plan, 1952; Publication (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Box: 2, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Safety and Operating Instructions for Engineers, Transportation Crew, Locomotive Crane Operators and Locomotive Crane Followers, 1950; Publication (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Box: 2, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Baltimore Works Stainless Bar and Wire Products, 1958; Publication (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Box: 2, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Noncontributory Pension Plan of Armco Steel Corp. & Subsidiaries, 1957; Publication (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Box: 2, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Contributory Retirement Income Plan for Employees of Armco Steel Corp. & Subsidiaries, 1955; Publication (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Box: 2, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Armco Policies, 1957; Publication (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Box: 2, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Blue Cross: The Best Way to Pay Hospital Bills, 1953; Publication (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Box: 2, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Preserve Competition-- Management's Job, 1950; Publication (Box 2, Folder 40)
    Author: Charles R. Hook
- Box: 2, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Changes in Program of Insurance Benefits Hourly Paid Employees, 1963; Publication (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Box: 2, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Supervisory Incentive Plan, Publication (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Box: 2, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Safe Practice Instructions Railroad Operations, Publication (Box 2, Folder 43)